Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Illuminat...
Illumination!
The year was 1985,
and the number one
show on TV was...
Evil Bratt!
The show starred young
Balthazar Bratt as a child prodigy
and criminal mastermind
bent on world domination.
There he is! Get him!
I've been a bad boy!
Bratt was the biggest
child actor of the 1980s,
striking a chord with
audiences all over the world.
There he is! Get him!
But it all came
to an end in Season 3, when...
I've been a bad boy!
The young star experienced
an unexpected growth spurt.
Boy? Ugh!
The show was canceled.
Hollywood rejected him
and Bratt quickly plunged
into a downward spiral,
starting to actually believe he was
the character he played on TV.
What are you looking at?
Leading us all to wonder,
where is he now?
You know what, Clive?
Playing a villain on TV was fun,
but being one in real life
is even better.
Heist music!
Here it comes.
What?
Clive, what are you doing?
How is that heist music?
Sorry. My bad.
Ew!
Mommy!
Stop or I'll...
Sir, the ship has been boarded
by some kind of monster!
Wait! That's not
a monster.
That's a man
wearing shoulder pads!
There's only one supervillain
whose fashion sense
is quite that dated.
Balthazar Bratt.
Blast it! The Dumont
Diamond is on that ship.
I want every agent in the area
on the scene immediately!
We're already here. Agents
Grucy are closing fast.
Yes! Wait.
What did you call us?
"Grucy." You know, GRU and
Lucy mushed together. Try it.
Oh! I like it,
but not a lot.
I don't like it.
Stop!
On the ground!
Go, go, go!
Eh?
Too late again, GRU!
Wha?
He's getting away!
That's what he thinks.
Go! Go! Go...
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
I don't think we
can make it, GRU!
We can make it!
No, we can't!
Ahh!
Get ready!
Get ready for...
Hey. How you doing?
Are you okay?
You guys are so cute.
Go get him, GRU-GRU!
Hello, GRU.
How's your transition coming?
You know, from world's
worst villain
to world's worst agent?
Oh, that's hilarious.
You should be on TV.
Oh, that's right. You were!
But then you got canceled!
Ha-ha!
What about that?
Ugh!
What? Oh, girls!
Oh!
Dance fight!
Ow!
Alpha Team, the diamond is secure.
Come and pick up the package.
Copy that.
Alpha Team in approach.
GRU!
Did you actually
think I was unconscious?
Huh! It's called acting, hoser.
And clearly, I've still got it!
I've been a bad boy!
Freeze! Don't move!
Son of a Betamax!
Go, go! Get him!
He's getting away!
This isn't over, GRU.
You hear me?
This is not over.
Yeah? Well,
I still have the diamond.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to...
Happy birthday, dear Dan
Happy birthday to you
I can't believe
Bratt got away again.
How is this
possible? How?
And it's not just
that he got away,
it is he's so smug about it.
"Ooh, I've been
a bad boy!"
Gah! Edna, hey!
Looking hot today.
Got cats on you.
And it was so humiliating, dangling
there in the bubble-gum Speedo.
And I didn't have time to
go to the gym this week,
and I had a big breakfast. And
was feeling a little bloated.
You know what? He's not
even worth talking about.
I don't even want to waste
another breath about the guy.
And another thing!
Next time I see Bratt, I will
moonwalk all over his stupid face!
Thank you all for coming
at such short notice.
It is with great sadness that I
inform you that, as of today,
I am retiring as
head of the AVL.
Oh, no!
Your new leader is coming
directly from head office.
Effective immediately.
She is the very gifted,
very ambitious,
Miss Valerie da Vinci.
As I look out
over all your faces,
I am flooded with
so many memories.
Oh, boy!
This is a snooze fest!
Excuse me, this is my last...
Blah, blah, blah!
We understand.
You're old, you're
fat, you're done.
Let me breathe in.
Ooh, broke a little sweat,
there.
First order of business,
which one of you losers
is Agent GRU?
Oh, that would be me.
Although, I don't know if
I'd say "loser," per se.
Kind of is...
Oh, it's the girls!
Not a good time.
Hey!
Ahh!
Yes, sir!
Uh...
Ma'am? You're making me nervous.
How could you let
Balthazar Bratt,
the AVL's most wanted villain,
just get away?
That is the opposite
of what we do here!
Okay, okay.
Yes, maybe
he got away. Again.
But he didn't get the diamond.
And I am this close
to bringing him in.
This close.
Huh. Interesting.
You're fired!
What?
That's totally not fair.
GRU is a great agent!
You know what?
If you fire him,
you're gonna have to
fire me, sister-sister.
And do you really wanna do that?
Do ya?
No, no, no!
Well, I guess she did.
Honey, you didn't
have to do that.
I know how much
you love your job.
Well, I love other things more.
You know, we're gonna
have to tell the girls.
Can you do it?
The whole "mom" thing
is still kind of new to me.
Oh, sure.
Huh?
Psst!
Hello?
Aloha!
Oh!
This is unexpected.
Well, you never got to
go on a honeymoon, so...
We made you dinner!
It's a luau!
We got pineapples and
coconuts and ukuleles!
Oh! Yay!
Yay!
The soup of the day.
Madame and Monsieur.
The gummy bears were my idea.
Mmm! Looks too good
to even eat.
Am I right?
But I made it for you. Oh.
Mmm-mmm-mmm!
Good soup!
I love the combination
of gummy bears
and meat.
I'm gonna hold it in my mouth.
'Cause it's so good, I
don't wanna swallow it.
So, how was work?
Ooh, did you take that guy down?
Did anything explode?
Well, actually,
today, Lucy and I were
invited to not work
at the AVL anymore.
No!
You got fired?
Oh, no!
No, no, no.
Yes.
But don't worry.
I'm sure we'll get
new jobs. Real soon.
Even better ones.
What's better than being
super-cool secret agents?
Ooh, I know!
You could gamble online!
That's what Katie's dad does.
Okay. We will definitely
look into that.
That's a good suggestion.
And let's not go over
to Katie's house anymore.
Hmm?
Guys! Shh! I don't think
you heard me right.
No, no, no.
This does not mean that we are
going back to being villains.
Okay, all right.
I get it.
Look, I know it's been
a little tough lately.
Especially with Dr. Nefario accidentally
freezing himself in carbonite.
But our life of crime is over!
Mel! Mel, you're
with me on this, right?
Guys, listen to me!
Read my lips!
What? What?
Oh... What did I say?
It's not "comquit"?
Ah, okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't take that tone with me!
We're not going back to villainy.
Yes! And I don't want to
hear another word about it.
Look, if you guys don't stop right
now, there will be consequences.
Hey! Don't say anything
you're going to regret.
What? You quit?
You're serious?
Come on!
Dave! Jerry!
Great news, guys.
You have been promoted.
You're in charge now.
Huh? Not bad.
Jeesh!
Ah, Monsieur Pompeux!
To what do we owe the presence
of the world's
foremost gem expert?
The chief of police sent me.
He was concerned that during
the recent heist attempt,
the Dumont Diamond
was replaced with a phony.
Ooh, la-la!
You have been duped!
What? We have?
Yes.
By me!
But, what is...
Oh, no! Help!
Ooh!
I've been a bad boy!
Or should I say...
Oh!
Hey, GRU.
What you doing down here?
In the dark. Alone.
Oh, nothing.
Just thinking.
You okay?
Oh, yes. Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
It's just...
I don't know.
I guess I just feel like
a failure.
Like I don't have
a purpose anymore.
Hey, mister,
you are not a failure.
If only I could
have nailed Bratt.
So many times, I almost had him.
But now I'll never
get the chance,
'cause I have been
kicked to the curb.
GRU, you've got to let this go.
It's time to look forward.
Things will get
better. I promise.
Excuse me.
Pardon me, young people?
Would you tell me
how to get to this address?
I'm looking for a Mr. GRU.
Idiots.
No! Kyle!
Stop! Kyle, let go!
No! No!
You've got to be kidding me!
Lucy, did you...
He helps you if
you have nightmares.
And he's really
good to snuggle with.
Oh, no, no, no.
Agnes! Agnes!
So take good care of him.
Thank you!
Agnes, what are you doing?
You sold your unicorn?
Well, I just wanted to help,
since you don't have a job.
I got two whole dollars for it.
Uh, excuse me?
Sorry, buddy, the sale's over.
Yes, but this will
only take a...
Hey, eyebrows, get off the lawn.
Yeah, but...
Hey, could you...
Oh, uh, of course.
Now, as I was saying, I...
Uh... Oh.
Goodbye!
Listen, Agnes, you don't need to worry.
We're going to be fine.
For real?
For real.
Now, come on, let's
pack this stuff up.
Ow! Ow!
Seriously?
Buddy, you're not
getting the hint.
Excuse me, Mr. GRU,
but I really must
have a word with you.
How do you know my name?
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Fritz.
Ow!
Good puppy.
And I am inquiring on behalf
of your twin brother, Dru.
He needs your help.
What? Twin brother?
Twin brother?
Oh, Ja.
He would like to fly you
to Freedonia to meet him.
Your father has recently
passed away and...
Okay, cuckoo.
I'm sorry, but my dad
died when I was a baby,
and I don't have any brother.
You got the wrong guy.
Really? Well, then,
how do you explain this?
Bellissimo!
Oh, hello, GRU.
Hi, Mom.
It's important to keep active
in one's golden years.
Oh!
There you are, you cutie, you.
Uh, these are my
diving instructors.
Vincenzo und Paolo.
Ciao, boys.
So, what do you want?
Mom, do I have a twin brother?
Ah! How did you find out?
Who told you?
Wait, what? It's true?
You never told me
I had a brother!
And you told me that Dad died of
disappointment when I was born.
Ja, Ja.
That was the agreement.
Agreement?
What are you talking about?
Shortly after you and
your brother were born,
your father and I divorced.
We each took one son
to raise on our own
and promised never to
see each other again.
Obviously,
I got second pick.
I have a brother!
Hey, girls! How are
things in Row B, huh?
I put together some fun
activities for the trip!
Who is up for some gin rummy?
Yeah, um...
We're good.
Oh, okay.
I'll just sit here
and play solitaire.
I hope I win.
I wonder what Dru
will be like. Ooh!
Maybe we'll have the twin thing
when you can read
each other's minds, no?
How cool would that be?
Um, super cool!
Ooh!
Freedonia!
Freedonia! Freedonia!
Hi, piggy, piggy!
Whoa!
Look at that house!
It's like a castle!
I can't wait to meet my brother!
Ugh. What's with
all the pigs?
This is the family business.
The largest pig farm in
the whole of Freedonia.
Okay, nice pig.
No! That's my
private part!
This pig has issues!
Please, come in.
Oh, this is amazing!
Ah, it's like the Sistine Chapel!
But with pigs.
My brother!
GRU!
Dru!
Oh!
Brother! I am hugging you!
I'm so happy!
After all of these years,
finally I'm meeting you!
Yup. All right.
Good.
Oh, look at that.
You must be the beautiful wife.
Beautiful?
Oh!
Stop it.
Sweet talker.
How is my brother
finding a wife like you
when he is so bald?
I'm joking!
These must be my nieces!
You're Agnes! You
are small with big eyes.
And it makes me wanna
put you into my pocket.
You can't do that!
I'm too big.
Edith! I can tell that you
are a little mischievous.
We're gonna have to make
a little trouble later.
I already have!
Ow! Ow! Please!
Why are you
doing that? Ow!
Fist bump for
mischievous behavior!
And Margo.
Oh, you are so mature!
I'm guessing...
Mmm... 15?
15?
She's 12. She looks 12
and will always be 12.
So, Dru, this place is amazing!
I mean, you just walk through
the doors and you're like...
Oh, it's nice, I guess, sure.
I'm not really into things.
- This is so cool!
- Look at that!
Oh, my gosh!
He's even got a helicopter!
This is the best!
Yes, the best!
All right, let's go home now.
Home? Why?
I don't know. This guy with
the mansion and the cars
and all of the hair, with the
silky smooth, luxurious hair.
I feel worse than
I did before I came.
But he's your brother, GRU.
Give this a chance.
Oh, I was thinking,
while GRU and I
catch up on some brother stuff,
you girls should go with Fritz.
He has a surprise for you!
Yay!
Awesome!
I love surprises!
Oh, this is perfect!
Mother-daughter bonding time.
Let's do it!
Woot-woot!
Bye! You boys
have fun!
Whoopi!
Now you can be as
evil as Balthazar Bratt
with the Evil Bratt
action figure.
Featuring music-activated
breakdance mode.
Also featuring bubblegum-launching
shoulder pads!
And the all-new
Mega Diamond Laser!
No more math!
I've been a bad boy!
The Mega Diamond Laser
does not actually incinerate books.
How could
Hollywood cancel a show
that produced toys
like this, Clive?
Evil Bratt was a masterpiece!
Does no one value
true art anymore?
It's a disgrace
and a travesty, sir.
Well, now that I've got the
diamond, it's payback time.
Oh, it's too bad GRU won't be
around to try and stop me.
Oh, wait! No, it's not.
I hate that dweeb!
And you, Hollywood!
This time, I'm canceling you
and all the losers
who rejected me!
Oh, piggy, piggy!
So, how are things going
for you career-wise?
Great!
So, so great!
Crushing it.
Well, I've got
something that I think
you will find very interesting.
Hold onto your face, brother.
Yee-haw!
Yah, yah!
Ow!
Come on!
What is all this?
The pig farm was just a cover
for the real family business.
Now, feast your eyes on
Dad's lair!
Ta-da!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
So, our dad was a villain?
No, no, no, not just a villain.
One of the greatest of all time!
He was known as the Bald Terror!
That's him? Our dad?
He was so proud of you. And
what a great villain you were.
He was?
But me, eh, not so much.
To Dad, I was just a failure.
He never thought I had what
it took to be a villain.
But now, you can help
me prove him wrong!
Brother,
teach me the art of villainy!
No.
No, no, no.
I can't do that.
What? But
it's our family tradition!
You can't say no to that!
Look, I'm sorry.
I left that life behind me.
End of story.
Oh.
Okay. I understand.
Hmm! I wonder
what this does.
Holy Moley!
Dad's villain wheels!
Pretty slick, huh?
Hey, you wanna take her out for a spin?
Just for some fun?
Mmm!
Oh, oh, oh! Look out!
What a beautiful day!
Zero to 400 in three seconds.
Able to withstand
a nuclear blast.
Armed to the teeth.
Okay, that's pretty nice.
And it's a hybrid.
Look out!
Help me!
I am not enjoying this.
Whoa! What is
going on here?
Welcome to the annual
Freedonian Cheese Festival.
Go!
Look, look!
Look at all the candies!
Whoa!
Eep, eep, eep!
Lucy, can we get these? Please.
Okay, but only
one each. I mean it.
Aw!
Oh, man!
No, I don't. Get as
many as you want. I don't care.
Yay! Awesome!
Uh...
What?
Well, it's okay to tell them
no sometimes, too, you know?
Moms need to be tough.
Right, right.
Tough. Good one.
I can totally do that.
You know, still figuring
out this mom thing.
Gettin' my sea legs, matey!
It's a unicorn!
Can we go in there?
Please, please, please!
Um... Sure! Yeah! You
know, but first let's...
Um...
Oh, look!
It's a traditional
Freedonian dance.
How amazing does that look?
Say, say, say cheese!
Cheese! I love this.
The little girls go and get the
cheese from the little boys.
That's adorable!
Aw, look at that poor little guy.
With his little boots.
Nobody picked him.
Oh, Margo, why don't
you go up there?
No way!
Okay.
Wait a minute.
No!
Go take a bite of
his cheese, young lady.
Right now!
What?
I'm being tougher, you know?
Like you said.
No! I meant be tougher on them.
Not me!
Oh, come on, just do it. What's
the worst that could happen?
Mmm...
Fine.
Wow!
Hey, there.
I'm Margo.
Hello, Margo!
I am Niko.
Would you like
some of my cheese?
Mmm...
Say, say, say cheese!
Yes! Thank you, Margo.
Thank you!
Bam! I am a great mother!
Did you see that, girls?
I laid down the...
Oh, no! Where are they?
Oh... Agnes? Edith?
Hello.
Look!
A unicorn horn!
My little brain is
going to explode!
Agnes, that's fake.
It's real, all right.
That horn came from
the Crooked Forest.
The only place on earth
where unicorns still live.
Huh!
Laugh, laugh, all of you.
They all think I'm crazy.
But I'm telling you,
I saw one once.
With my own eye.
Wait, wait, wait. You saw
a for-real live unicorn?
What did it look like?
Did you pet it?
Did it smell like candy?
Was it fluffy?
It was so fluffy,
I thought I was gonna die.
Mmm! Do you think maybe
I could find one, too?
Oh! They say if a maiden
pure of heart
goes into the Crooked Forest,
the unicorn will
come and be hers.
Forever.
Hmm...
Agnes!
Goal!
Excuse me.
Girls, don't worry.
I'm here.
Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Are you?
Unicorns are really real!
And I'm gonna find one!
Sorry. Went a little
mama bear on ya.
You know,
I heard a scream and...
Yeah, okay, have a good one.
Wait for me here.
Stop that!
Ah! You kicked me.
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Did you just steal candies? Yes!
That's a lot of effort
for two lollipops.
Oh, no! The police!
What do we do?
Come on!
This is gonna be fun!
The police are gonna get us!
I'm freaking out!
Pigs!
Cops!
Whoa! They're back!
All right!
Oh, man, that was crazy!
We were so close
to getting busted.
Tell me about it.
I thought you were going
to pee your pants.
I did!
You did!
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Hey! What are
you doing?
Intruders! Intruders!
There they are! Stop!
Hey, you, don't move!
Halt!
Call for backup!
Ooh, uh...
Get 'em! Go! Go!
Hey, you!
Freeze! Don't move!
Hands in the air!
Face it, GRU. Villainy
is in your blood.
You can't tell me you don't
miss the rush. A little?
Uh...
Eh, maybe a little.
And now you've got the
chance to get back on top.
Get your mojo back.
Become GRU again. How
awesome would that be?
Hmm.
Oh, please, come on.
Just one heist.
There's got to be something
out there, somewhere
that you still wanna steal.
Huh.
There is something.
How about we steal
the largest diamond
in the world?
Yes! I love it!
Oh, thank you, brother!
Thank you from
the bottoms of my heart.
Oh, you know what? We should
do something to celebrate!
Oh!
I've got the perfect idea.
Fritz, my good fellow, could you
get me another napkin, please?
Ah, yes.
Of course, Miss Edith.
Hey, where are GRU and Dru?
Here we are!
Oh, how's it going?
It's me! GRU.
And me, Dru.
I hug everybody whether
they like it or not.
Why are they pretending
to be each other?
Ah! What's for dinner?
I probably won't like it.
I'm so grumpy
all the time. Hmm.
I laugh a lot.
And I'm kind of an idiot!
Oh, I'm busting a gut!
Look at them!
They had no idea!
Total burn.
Oh, look, it's me, GRU!
And I'm Dru!
We switched places!
Oh, it's so nice to see
you two are getting along.
Oh, we're getting...
Along perfectly.
Wait. Did we...
Just finish...
Each...
Other's...
Sentences?
Oh, that's delightful.
Not creepy at all.
And you're gonna stop
now though, right?
Sorry, it's a twin thing.
Uh-huh...
So, uh, what did
you guys do today?
Nothing.
Okay.
What does it...
All done!
Pardon me! Out of the way!
Good night, everybody!
Hey! Hey! Put the brakes on.
What's the rush?
I need to get to bed so I can
wake up and find a unicorn!
Good night!
What was that about?
Agnes thinks she's gonna find a
real unicorn in the woods tomorrow.
She's totally freaking out.
I feel like someone's
gotta tell her the truth.
Not it!
Oh, don't worry.
Parenting 101. I got this.
Um...
And please bless that
when I find the unicorn
he'll want to come home with
me, and sleep in my room.
And that I can ride him
to school every day.
And he'll use his magical
powers to help me do math.
Amen.
Oh, hi, GRU.
Hey. So, big day tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm finally gonna get
to see a unicorn. For reals.
If I do, can I bring it home?
Please?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Tell you what, every unicorn you
find, you can bring it home.
I'd better build
a big pen, right?
But, you know,
there's a chance that
you might not find one.
Huh?
It might not be good
unicorn-finding weather.
Um... They're tricky
to find them.
And I don't know.
Maybe...
Maybe unicorns
don't really
explore that part of the woods.
But the man said a maiden could
find one if she was pure in heart.
And I'm pure in heart, right?
The purest.
Can we stop talking now?
I need to get to sleep.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, GRU.
Unicorns, I love them
Huh!
I'm okay.
Hey! Give
that back!
Oh, no! Run!
We've been waiting
a long time. Can we...
No!
No, please!
GRU?
Uh-oh!
Ha!
Huh?
Because
I'm training for the big day
Nobody's gonna stop me
'Cause I am super sassy
Super sassy, super sassy
What's today's plan, boss?
What's the plan?
Silly robot.
I'll show you the plan!
Time to watch a very special
episode of Evil Bratt
to see exactly what I'm gonna
do to stupid Tinseltown.
This week on Evil Bratt...
It's a giant Evil Bratt robot!
Open fire!
I have him in my sights!
Nice try, coppers!
Chew on this!
He's shooting his super sticky,
self-inflating gum!
Run!
Gum one, gum all!
"Gum one, gum all."
Seriously, how did this
show never win an Emmy?
And now, it's your turn
to shine, my diamond!
Hey, Clive. I guess you
could say our plan was
out of this world!
Now, that's entertainment!
Come on!
Let's make it a reality!
Here we are, in the dark
and creepy Crooked Forest
in search of
the mythical unicorn.
For some reason.
And here she is! The fearless
unicorn hunter seeking...
Edith, stop it!
You're gonna scare
away the unicorn.
If, somehow, we actually
find a unicorn,
I'm gonna film it and get rich.
Look over there!
Whoa!
This is it!
This is where we're
gonna see it.
Unicorns, here we come.
What's that for?
Bait! Duh.
Come on!
Now, all we have to do is wait.
Okay, this is Bratt's lair.
It may not look like much,
but this place is
armed with some of
the most high-tech
weaponry known to man.
It's considered impenetrable.
But a piece of cake
for us, right, brother?
Yes. This is not
like stealing lollipops.
Whoa!
His security system can detect an
air assault from any direction.
Ouch! No! Ouch!
Please, stop! Ouch!
So we'll have to approach low
and close to the water.
Next. Ah...
Then there are
these deadly spikes.
Geronimo!
Covered with enough
poison to blow your mind.
Literally.
Ouch!
Ah, good to know.
So here's the plan.
You're the getaway driver.
So you'll wait in the boat...
Wait, hold on!
Wait in the boat?
But I wanna be
in on the actions!
Dru, the getaway driver is the
most crucial part of any plan.
Do you know how hard it is
doing nothing, touching nothing
when all of that adrenaline
is coursing through your veins
and you must wait?
Can I count on you?
Yeah.
Ah, I guess so.
So, I'll climb up to
the cube and enter here.
Then once I'm inside,
find the diamond.
I've underestimated Bratt before.
It's not going to be easy.
I think we can handle it.
Dad's villain suits!
This will make us unstoppable!
Whoa! Ay, chihuahua!
I call the black one.
It's go time!
Hello.
Oh, hi!
Hello, mother of Margo.
I am Niko.
I present you
with pig to confirm
my engagement to your daughter.
Hey, what now?
What's going on?
Uh, remember little boots?
Hello, my schmoopsie poo.
Whoa, hey!
He seems to think you're engaged.
What? We're
not engaged.
Look, Niko, you seem like a very
nice boy with a very nice pig.
Uh... But you're
not engaged.
Okay? It's not
happening.
I understand.
Who was I kidding?
A dumpling like me
with a goddess like you.
But I promise, I will
never forget you, Margo.
Never.
Oh, I'm pretty sure I won't
forget you either.
Bye. Bye, Niko.
Wow! That was crazy.
Whoa!
That was totally humiliating.
Taking a bite of that cheese was the
stupidest thing I've ever done.
Why did I listen to you?
Right. But it's over
now, so...
Oh! Here we go.
Niko...
You refuse my
son's engagement pig?
What?
May you and your
daughter die a slow death
and be buried with onions.
All right, lady, that's it!
Nobody...
Nobody curses my daughter!
Ya got that?
Because if you mess with
Margo, you mess with me!
And I promise, you do
not wanna mess with me.
Do you understand me?
Yes. Yes.
Good.
Now get!
Look, Margo, I think
we just need to... Oh.
Yes!
I have to tell GRU!
Can we go back now?
Already? Just
a couple more hours.
We have to be home
before it gets dark.
I don't understand.
I did exactly what the man said.
You mean that one-eyed scar-faced
man that everybody laughed at?
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Look, Agnes, maybe we're not...
Ooh, my whole life has been
building to this moment.
Um... It's a...
Unicorn!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna name you Lucky!
Oh, Lucky, stop it!
Yeah, I'll let someone
else burst her bubble.
Look at us! Two brothers
pulling a heist!
And that diamond will
make us the richest,
most powerful
villains in the world!
Right, brother?
Oh, right. Yep, yeah.
Bravo! Bravissimo!
You're amazing!
I'm so sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
I was very rude.
And you were always such a gentleman.
You did it!
You got our jobs back!
What?
Oh, yeah, right. Sure.
Oh, look.
We're here!
I'm going in. Take the wheel.
I still don't see why
I can't go with you.
Hey, hey!
We discussed this.
Now is not the time
to mess with the plan.
Fine.
Ha-ha!
Hey, brother!
What? I told you, you are
supposed to stay with the boat!
Oh, I didn't think you
meant that literally.
What other way
could I have meant it?
All right. Let's move.
Just follow my lead.
Got it.
Whoa!
Help me!
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh, no! The poison spikes!
I'm gonna be impaled!
I'm okay.
I miss the minions.
Come on!
Coming.
Come on.
It's a scanning device.
Quick!
Camouflage mode.
Freeze! And
close your eyes!
And cover your mouth!
Okay, take my hand.
Ha-ha! Follow me.
Ha-ha!
Look out!
Oh, you were right. I should
have stayed in the boat.
My stomach feels all queasy.
I shouldn't have
eaten that pot pie.
Hey, hey, relax.
You're gonna be just fine.
I got your back.
Come on. This way.
Huh?
Hmm?
Looks like it's right above us.
Okay, what do I do?
Should I wait in the vent?
No, come with me.
Dru, get off the bed!
Yes, I'd like to
thank the Academy...
I can help.
No, no, no.
What? I can do it.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Why, yes.
Yes, Molly Ringwald, I will take
you to the prom.
What? Who? Where? What?
Who's there? Who is there?
99 of red balloons
Whoops! Almost forgot!
Over here.
Stay close.
What?
Dolls.
Looks like Bratt
was the only one
stupid enough to buy this junk.
Oh, I used to have one of these!
Ow!
Hey! Shh! Come on.
All right.
We're getting close.
From now on,
every move must be made
with total
precision and purpose.
Gum!
Focus!
We're after the diamond,
not the bubblegum.
Got it!
Mmm. Yum.
This way!
And now, to put this
where it belongs.
What...
Look at it, Clive.
It's beautiful!
Will you please shut up?
He's gonna spot us!
Spit it out! Spit it out!
I told you not to touch anything!
Intruders!
Intruders! Intruders!
Freeze, dipsticks!
GRU? There's two
of you now?
Then this will be twice as much fun.
GRU.
Give me back my diamond!
Total lockdown!
Oh!
Go get 'em, Bratt Pack!
They're gonna get us!
Run!
Oh, no!
What does that mean?
Are we gonna die?
We're gonna die!
Dru!
What?
Hey, guys. Hold on!
Lucy!
Thank you for saving us.
Whoo!
Look! We got the diamond
and we're going to...
Take it to the AVL
and get our jobs back.
Wait!
What? Oh,
that's amazing!
And the best part is,
you'll never...
ever go behind my back...
ever again, right, honey bear?
Yeah! Yeah, right.
Lesson learned.
I'll get the girls
and start packing.
And tell them the good news!
Ah! We're getting
our jobs back. Yeah!
Yes! Yes!
Go tell the girls.
Dru...
No! No way! We can't
give the diamond back!
I have to.
No, you don't!
Yes, I do.
- Give it!
- No!
Give it!
Ow!
What is wrong with you?
You kicked me!
You... You lied to me!
Hey, I would have
told you the truth.
But you're too much
of a wimp to handle it.
That's it.
I'm out of here.
You have no right to take that.
We stole it together.
Together?
You got to be kidding me.
You did nothing but screw up
the whole time.
I got this in spite of you.
Oh, yeah? At least I didn't
get fired from my job
like a total loser.
At least I had a job.
What have you accomplished
that was so great?
I'll tell you what. Nothing!
No wonder Dad thought
you were such a failure.
We are no longer brothers.
That's fine with me.
GRU! I found
a unicorn!
My life is complete!
Honey, that's...
That's not actually a unicorn.
Huh?
But, but, he has one horn.
I'm...
I'm sorry, sweetie...
but he's just a goat.
Life is just
like that sometimes.
We're hoping for a unicorn,
and we get a goat.
Well, you know what?
Lucky is the best goat
in the whole wide world!
Look at that face! I
just want to squeeze it.
Mmm!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
I'll take this.
You've been a bad boy, GRU.
Can you get the rest
of the suitcases?
Come on, girls.
Let's go!
Let's get physical, physical
Change of plans, girls.
Instead of going home...
Eyebrows! Ow!
We're going to Hollywood!
Now, that's what I call acting.
Let's go, Clive!
We've got a giant robot waiting!
Huh?
Lucy?
But...
Bratt! He took the girls!
What? No!
Dru! Dru!
Go away!
I don't wanna talk to you.
Bratt has the girls!
Listen, brother.
About what I said...
No, I'm the one...
But I shouldn't have...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, GRU.
Aw!
Ooh, look out!
What is that?
Mel?
GRU?
Hello, Hollywood!
I'm back and bigger than ever.
I'm scared!
Thank you.
Thank you so... Oh!
No! No!
No, you can't leave me here!
I'm famous!
Clive, arm the canons.
Chew on this!
Hey, mullet head!
Let us out!
Oh, don't worry, girls. I've
prepared a front row seat for you.
Agnes!
Once again, I win and GRU loses!
Enjoy the show, girls.
What in the heck?
Oh!
I hope the girls are okay.
Bratt! Bratt at nine o'clock...
No! Three o'clock!
He's on the left!
No!
I've seen this episode!
He's going to bubblegum the whole
city and send it up into space!
Hurry!
This is it! This is it!
Lights! Camera!
Laser!
Yeah!
Look!
I've got the girls. You
two, go take care of Bratt.
Wait! What are
you doing?
Look, you guys, it's Lucy!
Lucy, over here!
Help! Help us!
Mama's comin', girls.
- Lucy! Lucy!
- We're up here!
Look at that laser go.
I love it when
a plan comes together.
It's GRU!
Get ready, Bratt.
You're about to be
blasted back to the '80s!
Whoo-hoo!
We got him!
Oh, no!
Don't worry.
There's more
where that came from.
It'll take more
than that to stop me.
Bratt Pack, go get that barf bag.
Oh, incoming!
You little...
Get away!
Get out of there!
Quick, jump!
Bonus!
Did you see that, Clive? All gone.
Buh-bye,
Wonder Twins.
Help!
Hang on!
Hang on, girls!
I've got you!
I can't! I'm slipping!
No!
Got ya!
Thank you, Lucy!
Let's go!
We're not safe yet.
Minions!
Look at what we have here.
Sorry, GRU. This is going to
be a total burn!
Oh, no! No, no, no!
I've been a bad boy!
Nobody messes with my brother!
What? What's happening? No!
Dru!
Hold on! I'm coming.
You've ruined everything!
And now, it's time to die.
Any last words, GRU?
You know what?
I got two words for you.
Dance fight.
Oh, it is on like Donkey Kong.
I am going to enjoy this.
Enough!
My turn!
Uh-oh.
Game over!
Is this what you're looking for?
No!
Curse you, GRU!
Curse you!
Dru? Dru?
Hey! We did it!
Yes, we did, brother.
- GRU!
- Uncle Dru!
GRU!
Girls!
Hey, Mel. Welcome back.
Mmm.
Love you, Mom.
I'm a mom.
I'm a mom!
Boys, time for bed!
We're back at work
in the morning.
I'm coming, sweetie.
Good night, Lucy.
See you tomorrow, brother.
Hey, I'm back on the job.
So no villainy tonight,
huh? Got it?
I make no promises.
Love you!
Uh-huh. Right.
I love you, too.
Aw!
"Aw!" All right, every...
Go! Go! Go to bed!
Hey! Guys! Come on!
What...
What is happening?
It's coming from outside!
Hey! I thought we
said no more villainy!
Sorry, brother!
Somebody's gotta keep the
family tradition alive, right?
Let's get him.
Ugh.
Honey, he's my brother.
We'll give him a
five-minute head start.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org